Trevor Bradford

Tunnel Hill, Ga. 425 Hasty Drive 706-581-9373

trevorscott1993@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Skilled computer science student with five years of experience with strong proficiency in Java, C#, JavaScript, and database management tools. Seeking full time or internship position where I can use my skills to enhance software development, web application projects, analyze problems, and accomplish business needs.

EDUCATION

Kennesaw State University - Kennesaw, GA Bachelor of Science, Computer Science Expected Graduation May 2020

ACADEMIC PROJECTS

Senior Project: Shaw Industries Meeting Room Kiosk

Group Research Project: 08/2019 - 12/2019

Project Goal: Create a conference room kiosk that integrates with their current Google Suite platform and provides analytics on room utilization.

Responsibilities:

- Create a website user interface through a combination of CSS/HTML, JavaScript, and jQuery.
- Generate all methods for Google API integration to obtain event information on shared calendar resources within the G-Suite platform.
- Assist in the development of a machine learning model to detect room occupants using OpenCV and Python.

SKILLS

Programming Languages: Java, C#, C++, JavaScript, and Python

Database Management: Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Access, SQL Server, and SQLite.

Frameworks and Technologies: .NET, SQL, ¡Query, Angular, CSS, HTML.

OS Platforms: Windows and Linux Methodologies: Agile development

Cloud Platform Experience in AWS and GCP

WORK EXPERIENCE

Amazon Warehouse Associate – January 2016 – Present

Chattanooga, TN

Amazon outbound problem solver associate

- Work in a team environment with fellow problem solvers that research problem shipments through an Amazon shipment database across all outbound functions including Pick, Pack, Sort, and Ship dock.
- Investigate lost items in the Amazon shipment database.
- Troubleshoot and reduce problem shipments to minimize issues and increase workflow.
- Collaborate with management and fellow problem solvers to ensure customer's orders are being fulfilled.

Amazon outbound pick associate / Seasonal Ambassador

- Process different merchandise in a warehouse environment using an RF scanner.
- Trained over 50 new associates for the pick direct function for 2 consecutive years as a seasonal ambassador while supervising and communicating with them on preventative barriers for their job.
- Assist in maintaining a safe work environment by eliminating hazardous conditions such as properly storing equipment, reporting liquid damages, and disposing of cardboard/plastics.

Wendy's Employee/Shift Manager - September 2011 - January 2016

Dalton, GA

- Generated and organized sales and inventory reports within Microsoft Excel.
- Communicated well and used interpersonal skills to make positive relationships with guests and employees.
- Organized and scheduled employees for day to day functions within the workplace.